Souray Dhali

UI/UX Designer

+8801634322217

souravdhali@protonmail.com

souravdhali.me



ABOUT

UI/UX designer with past experience in design, communication and marketing. Previously working with webconbd, mynt connect and pathao which help me a lot to understand creative fields, effective communications and how to interact with users or followers. Undertook UI/UX design training to become an effective solution maker. Skilled in research, user flow, wireframe, visual design, presentation design, prototyping in figma and adobe XD to create simple user oriented design solutions for web, iOS and android.

UX PROJECT

April, 2022 - August, 2022

My Airtel App - UI/UX Redesign Case Study

View Case Study →

"My Airtel" app is a mobile application that tries to provide one-stop solutions to all airtel network users.

CERTIFICATION

UI/UX Design Essential

Udemy

July 19, 2020

EXPERIENCE

June 2021 - December 2021

Design Intern

Webconbd

I was responsible for participating in user research and interaction studies, translating user stories and business requirements into effective designs, and designing sitemaps, wireframes, prototypes, and UI.

December 2020 - June 2021

Social Media Executive

MYNT Connect

As a social media executive, I was responsible for creating shareable contents, determining which platform is best suited for each content, social media campaign and analyzing performance of those campaign; managing Facebook pages and also managing quarries and so on.

April, 2018 - September, 2018

Support Officer

Pathao LTD

As a customer care executive, I was responsible for answering calls and provide information about products and services. Besides, I had to maintain data entry as well.

SKILLS

User Research
Flow Diagram
Wireframe
Visual Design
Prototyping
Mockups

Presentation Design
Usability testing
Basic HTML/CSS

TOOLS

Figma Miro Notion Visual Design

Adobe applications

EDUCATION

2016 - 2020

Master of Business Administration

BRAC University

Marketing

2012 - 2015

Bachelor Of Science

Patuakhali Science and Technology University

Agriculture